https://www.technokids.com/privacy-policy.aspx

×
Your Promotional Discount is in effect! HAPPY HOLIDAY EVENT | 35% Off any regular priced technology project or collection. No limit. Offer not available on sales items.[Expires: Thursday, December 31, 2020. Discount will be applied at checkout.]
HomePrivacy Policy
Privacy Policy
TechnoKids Inc. is committed to protecting your privacy. You can visit most pages on our site without giving us any information about yourself. But sometimes we do need information to provide services that you request, and this privacy statement explains data collection and use in those situations. This privacy statement applies to TechnoKids.com and TechnoKids.ca; it does not apply to other online or offline TechnoKids Inc. sites, products or services. Please read the complete privacy statement.
Collection of Personal Information
We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you (personal information) or allows us to contact you. Generally, this information is requested when you are ordering email newsletters, joining a limited-access premium site, signing up for an event or training, or when purchasing and/or registering TechnoKids Inc. products. Personal information collected by TechnoKids.com and TechnoKids.ca often is limited to email address, name, country or location, but may include other information when needed to provide a service you requested. For example: If you choose a service or transaction that requires payment, such as making a purchase through our Web site, we will request personal information necessary for billing and/or shipping, such as:
address, telephone number, and credit card number. When you buy and install a new product, we may ask you to register your purchase electronically. We keep this registration information on file with any information you've already given us on previous visits to our Web site.
Use of Personal Information
Personal information is used for the following reasons:
To ensure our site is relevant to your needs.
To deliver services, such as newsletters, events, training or software, that you request or purchase.
To help us create and publish content most relevant to you.
To alert you to product upgrades, special offers, updated information and other new services from TechnoKids Inc., if you so request.
To allow you access to limited-entry areas of our site as appropriate.
TechnoKids Inc. may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to:
conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on TechnoKids Inc. or the site
protect and defend the rights or property of TechnoKids Inc. and its family of Web sites, or act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of TechnoKids Inc. employees, users of TechnoKids Inc. products or services, or members of the public.
Your information may be stored and processed in Canada or any other country in which TechnoKids Inc. or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using this site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. TechnoKids Inc. abides by the safe harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of data from the European Union.
Control of Personal Information
When you give us personal information, TechnoKids.Inc will not share that information with third parties without your permission, other than for the limited exceptions already listed. It will only be used for the purposes stated above.
Cookies
The www.technokids.com website uses "cookies", a technology that installs tiny data files on the user's computer in order to allow the website to recognize future visits using that computer. One of the largest benefits of Cookies is that they allow the web server to maintain state with the client browser throughout a multi-step process such as completing a contact form or making a purchase on-line. All this is accomplished without sending any personal information to the Website. Many browsers are initially set up to accept cookies but you may choose to disable the use of or decline cookies if your browser permits or set your browser to indicate when a cookie is being sent, but in doing so you will affect your browsing experiences while visiting our Website and may affect your ability to experience and/or utilize all of the features of this Website.
Security of Personal Information
TechnoKids.Inc is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. For example, we store the personal information you provide in computer servers with limited access that are located in controlled facilities.
Enforcement of Privacy Statement
If you have questions regarding this statement, you should first contact TechnoKids.Inc by email.
Changes to this Statement
TechnoKids.Inc will occasionally update this privacy statement. When we do, we will also revise the "last updated" date at the top of the privacy statement. For material changes to this statement, TechnoKids.com will notify you by placing prominent notice on the website.
Contact Information
TechnoKids Inc. welcomes your comments regarding this privacy statement, please contact us by email or postal mail.
TechnoKids.com Privacy
TechnoKids Inc.
447 Kerr Street,
Oakville, ON L6K 3C2
Canada
